https://insightcenter.org/about-us/policies/

Privacy Policy
We are concerned about your privacy and the security of personal information you may submit to our website. Any information you give us will be held with the utmost care and security and will not be used in ways you have not consented. The Center does not collect any personal information except when it is specifically and knowingly provided.
We may share aggregate or summary information about visitors to our website for marketing purposes that in no way identifies the personal information provided by any individual. We do not sell, rent, share or release any personal identifying information.
The Insight Center, however, does reserve the right to collaborate with other similarly interested organizations for educational purposes such as public talks, retreats, seminars, classes or other events whose expressed purpose is to further our mission. To accomplish these ends, we may combine our lists with our collaborators and deliver them to a professional mailing house for automated processing.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Contact forms and Cookies
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
How long we retain your data
For users that register on our website, we also store the personal information provided in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Refund and Credit Policy
All Insight Center events and products have a satisfaction guarantee.
If you are unsatisfied, contact us and we will do everything possible to make you happy.
For individual events with advance registration, partial refunds will be provided up to 5 business days prior to the start of the event. For multi-day events or events with a multi-module teaching sequence, partial refunds will be provided up to 14 business days prior to the start of the first segment of the event sequence. For guest teacher events, partial refunds may be provided up to 14 days prior to the event. However, if a space for which a refund is requested is filled, a full refund less bank processing fees (5%) will be issued as long as a written request is received (email is fine) prior to the start of the event.
In special cases a partial refund may be provided after the start of an event if warranted.  Each request is considered on its merits. Credits will be honored through the close of the calendar year in which they were issued. For professional trainings, concerns related to quality of instructional content or delivery will be reviewed appropriately.
Continuing Education
The Insight Center is authorized by the American Psychological Association (APA) to provide continuing education units (CEUs) for psychologists.  The California Board of Behavioral Sciences accepts APA CEUs for the professionals it authorizes (LMFTs, LCSWs, LPCCs).  Continuing education units require full attendance at CE events and partial credit is never available.  CE certificates must be purchased within thirty (30) days of the event for which they are issued.
Professional Standards
We are committed to the finest quality of continuing education available. Any concerns related to course content or instruction can be discussed with the instructor during a break within the course itself or emailed to the address below.
We at the Center have a zero tolerance for any abuse of power and authority. We adhere to a clearly defined set of standards and practices to both prevent such problems from arising and respond appropriately to complaints.
We have adopted policies and procedures to properly handle the widest range of concerns. You can review these documents by downloading the following files:
Ethical Standards
Grievance Procedures
To submit a grievance contact:
Michael Shiffman, Executive Director
310-479-7996
grievance@insightcenter.org
Share This Page
Browse Classes
Join Our Mailing ListAdd yourself to our mailing list or update the lists you currently subscribe to so you will receive emails from us only in your areas of interest.
Learn More
Save the Dates PLEASE NOTE:  ALL Insight Center activities are being conducted via Zoom as virtual events.  Join us in the privacy of your home for innovative and creative trainings.
___________________________________________________________________
